[
    {
        "question": "The doctor said to the patient, \"You did not take the right medicine.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "the patient",
          "1": "medicine",
          "3": "that",
          "2": "said",
          "5": "take",
          "6": "the patient",
          "7": "the",
          "8": "had",
          "9": "to",
          "10": "not",
          "11": "the",
          "12": "right",
          "13": "taken",
          "14": "did"
        },
        "answers":[[7,2,9,4,3,6,8,10,13,11,12,1]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rabi said, \"I shall not start without you.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "me",
          "1": "not",
          "3": "you",
          "2": "Rabi",
          "5": "I",
          "6": "that",
          "7": "would",
          "8": "start",
          "9": "should",
          "10": "he",
          "11": "without",
          "12": "said"
        },
        "answers":[[2,12,6,10,7,1,8,11,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "I told you, \"I shall not start without him.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "I",
          "1": "start",
          "3": "told",
          "2": "would",
          "5": "not",
          "6": "I",
          "7": "you",
          "8": "him",
          "9": "should",
          "10": "that",
          "11": "without"
        },
        "answers":[[4,3,7,10,6,9,5,1,11,8],[6,3,7,10,4,9,5,1,11,8]]
    },
    {
        "question": "He told me, \"You will not start without me.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "he",
          "1": "that",
          "3": "me",
          "2": "should",
          "5": "start",
          "6": "I",
          "7": "would",
          "8": "not",
          "9": "without",
          "10": "told",
          "11": "him"
        },
        "answers":[[4,10,3,1,6,2,8,5,9,11]]
    },
    {
        "question": "The workers said, \"We will not work today.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "work",
          "1": "day",
          "3": "they",
          "2": "said",
          "5": "will",
          "6": "the",
          "7": "that",
          "8": "would",
          "9": "today",
          "10": "not",
          "11": "workers",
          "12": "that"
        },
        "answers":[[6,11,2,12,3,8,10,4,7,1],[6,11,2,7,3,8,10,4,12,1]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jesus said, \"We should love our neighbours.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "should",
          "1": "that",
          "3": "Jesus",
          "2": "we",
          "5": "love",
          "6": "they",
          "7": "our",
          "8": "said",
          "9": "neighbours",
          "10": "their",
          "11": "will"
        },
        "answers":[[3,8,1,2,4,5,7,9]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ruchira said, \"You should go to bed early.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "bed",
          "1": "you",
          "3": "that",
          "2": "will",
          "5": "Ruchira",
          "6": "to",
          "7": "I",
          "8": "go",
          "9": "said",
          "10": "early",
          "11": "should"
        },
        "answers":[[5,9,3,7,11,8,6,4,10]]
    },
    {
        "question": "We said, \"We can do it, and we must do it.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "we said",
          "1": "do that",
          "3": "and",
          "2": "we can",
          "5": "that",
          "6": "we must",
          "7": "we could",
          "8": "do that"
        },
        "answers":[[4,5,7,8,3,6,1],[4,5,7,1,3,6,8]]
    },
    {
        "question": "The teacher taught, \"The earth moves round the sun.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "moved",
          "1": "taught",
          "3": "moving",
          "2": "the",
          "5": "moves",
          "6": "that",
          "7": "round",
          "8": "the earth",
          "9": "the sun"
        },
        "answers":[[2,1,6,8,5,7,9]]
    },
    {
        "question": "My father always said, \"All work and no play makes Jack a dull boy.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "father",
          "1": "Jack",
          "3": "play",
          "2": "made",
          "5": "said",
          "6": "all",
          "7": "makes",
          "8": "my",
          "9": "that",
          "10": "and",
          "11": "dull",
          "12": "work",
          "13": "a",
          "14": "always",
          "15": "boy",
          "16": "no"
        },
        "answers":[[8,4,14,5,9,6,12,10,16,3,7,1,13,11,15]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Pushpita told me, \"English is easy to learn.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "learn",
          "1": "me",
          "3": "to",
          "2": "Pushpita",
          "5": "that",
          "6": "the",
          "7": "was",
          "8": "told",
          "9": "easy",
          "10": "English",
          "11": "learning"
        },
        "answers":[[2,8,1,5,10,7,9,3,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "She told me, \"I was waiting for the bus yesterday.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "the bus",
          "1": "had",
          "3": "was",
          "2": "for",
          "5": "before",
          "6": "she",
          "7": "waiting",
          "8": "day",
          "9": "that",
          "10": "she",
          "11": "me",
          "12": "the",
          "13": "waited",
          "14": "told",
          "15": "yesterday",
          "16": "been"
        },
        "answers":[[10,14,11,9,6,1,16,7,2,4,12,8,5],[6,14,11,9,10,1,16,7,2,4,12,8,5]]
    },
    {
        "question": "The team shouted, \"We were winning the match.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "winning",
          "1": "they",
          "3": "saying",
          "2": "the match",
          "5": "the team",
          "6": "that",
          "7": "been",
          "8": "and",
          "9": "shouted",
          "10": "had",
          "11": "said"
        },
        "answers":[[5,9,3,6,1,10,7,4,2]]
    },
    {
        "question": "She said, \"I was sleeping when Jaya called.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "called",
          "1": "sleeping",
          "3": "Jaya",
          "2": "she",
          "5": "she",
          "6": "that",
          "7": "had been",
          "8": "was",
          "9": "said",
          "10": "had",
          "11": "when"
        },
        "answers":[[5,9,6,2,7,1,11,3,10,4],[2,9,6,5,7,1,11,3,10,4]]
    }
]